[Music] The
reason for writing is that this is going towards repeat for the city,
so let's see the details of this company. This
company is Tablet
Financial Holding, in which ICICI
Bank has 64%
and this Fer Fer Financial Holding had
exited by selling its shares in 2019 and the
amount I am sharing is around 2000 crores
market share of the company. The company is the largest in the
insurance sector if we talk about it as of March 31st.
[Music] The
network of the company is quite solid
and they have
hospitals and
their tyre
company is continuously working on its expansion and is
focusing a lot on the company
and let's
look at the core parameters of the company.
But the company's pay date is around 35 crores
which is very low. After the income paris
of the company, the company has all the reserves, the
current share price of 1500 is 1000 and let's
look at the sales data.  The
sales of the company were increasing
around March
in operating profit of the company
[music]
from last year which is
around 89 paise last year the company sorry so there is class in apps
also nine coming on to the company
reserves the company has increased its results in the coming
air the result of the company in March 19 was
4946 crores which will increase to around 842 crores in 22 this
this
company increased its reserves in the last year the
company interest in
21 the debt is
around 485 sorry 485 [music] crores and in 22 it can be
reduced to around 35 crores this
was the company virtual debt free
return
was 25% which in 22
also take a
look at the company button the data
I took from June 21 to September 22 the
promoter holding
was around 48.02% in June 21 because the holding was reduced to
29.75% in September 22  The September profit has been reduced to
around 24.07%, which is
very low. The
company is net profitable. The data we are discussing here is the
consulted profit data of the company from the
last two quarters. If I talk about it
after March 22, in June 22 the company
was in good profit and in September there is a
lot of jam in net profit. The
net profit in September-June 22 was
around Rs 300.49 crore, which became
around Rs 22.53 crore in September,
around Rs 65.4 crore and if you observe the chart closely
then the stock is now showing a kind of
reversal and there is a possibility that in the
city